Peter Wexler papers 1965 - ongoing
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Papers., Series:I
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Engineering. Starnet. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Pre-Engineering Study. 1987 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Facility Set-ups. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Vehicles Seizes and Turning Radius. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Facility Footprints. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - PWI Engineering Analysis. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Engineering Schedule. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Electrical Requirements. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - PSI Charts. Information. undated (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Soil Compaction. Engineering Study. 1987 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Sole Source Paperwork. 1987 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Consultants. 1986 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Original Paperwork. 1986 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Metropolitan Philharmonic. Set-ups. Stage Orchestra. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Consultant Cost Analysis. 1987 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Summary List Updates. 1988 (Box 62)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Family Tree. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - As Submitted 10/15/86. 1986 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Operating Organization Proposal. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Venue Visit Reports. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Press and Public Relations. 1987 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Contract History. City. Metropolitan Philharmonic. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Memorandum. 3 folders. 1985-1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Transmittals. 2 folders. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Concerts. Business. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Photos. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Jaffe Sound. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - System Specification. 2 copies. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Value Engineering Report. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Sound Memorandum. 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Electrical Engineering Memorandum. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Electrical Engineering Specs. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Structural Truss. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Structural Engineer Contract. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Structural Engineer Memorandum. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Tension Structure Specs. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Tension Structure Memorandum. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Architect Specifications. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Architect Memorandum. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Architect Contract. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Structural. Electric. Bid Package Information. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Structural Engineering Specs. 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Structural. Electrical. Bid Package. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Structural. Electrical. Bids Received. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Prop Truck. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Magic Stage Information. 1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Other Venues. 1986-1988 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Consultants. 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Schedules. 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Prospective Contractors. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Contractor Tracking Sheets. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - General Contractor Resumes. 1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Vendor Contracts. undated (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Design. 1988-1989 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Item Lists. 1988 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Metropolitan Philharmonic City Contract. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Budget Background. 1988-1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Budget. 1988-1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Certificate of Substantial Completion. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Project Completion Sign-Offs. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Cranes and Derricks Permit. 1990-1991 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - E 214B Submission Preparation. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Completion Markers, as submitted. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Completion Markers, back-up. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Blank Forms E 124B. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - E 214 Back-up. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - E 214B as submitted. 4 folders. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Final E 214B Submission. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - D.G.S Forms. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Monthly reports as submitted to the City. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - QMF Agreement and Permits. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - NYC Guide for Design Consultant. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - DGS. Forms Re: Quickway. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - DGS. Forms Re: Maryland. Sound. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - DGS. Forms Re: Bash. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - LBE. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - DGS. General. 1986-1988 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - DGS. Forms Samples Completed. 1988-1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - QMF Preliminary Contracts. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Bash Preliminary Contracts. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - MSI Preliminary Contracts. 1989 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - QMF Contract Changes/Park Corr. 1990 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Contractors. MSI Copy of Final Contract. 1989-1991 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Subcontractors. QMF Final Contract. 1989-1991 (Box 64)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Subcontractors. Bash Final Contract. 1989 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Wexler Contrac. Correspondence. 1988 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - FTL Contract. Correspondence. 1989-1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Jaffe Contract. Correspondence. 1989-1991 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Wexler Signed Contract. 1987-1989-1991 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Jaffe Signed Contract. 1990-1991 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Contracts. Production Art LTG. 1989 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Consultants. Starnet. 1987-88 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Board of Estimate Approval. 1989 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Insurance Forms and Correspondence. 1989-1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Insurance as submitted to the City. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Insurance. Originals. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - NYC Insurance Subcontractors Bonds. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Workman's Comp. Originals. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Truck Drawings Blank. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Possible Vendors. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Scope of Work Options. 1989 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Scope of Work. 1989-1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Items Final. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Items Lists. 1989-1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - QMF Transportation Insurance. 1991 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - City Contract. Memorandum. 1989-1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - City Contract Cop. and Op. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. -Subcontract Rider Re: City. 1989 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Extension Request Correspondence. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Extension Document. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Second Extension Letter. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Final Extension Letter. 1990 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Metropolitan Philharmonic. Final Contract. Incomplete Signatures. 1990-1991 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Metropolitan Philharmonic. Final Contract Unsigned. 1990-1991 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts. - Budget Notes Pre-Phase III. 1989 (Box 65)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Tax Exempt L Forms. 1989 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Budget Material. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - J. Pollak Back-up Material. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Budget Material C. Gilchriest Back-up Material. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Current Budgeting Capital. 1989-1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Cash Flow Current Final. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Summary of Expenses. 1989 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Operations Budgeting. 1988-1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Budget Back-up Capital. 1989-1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Budget PWI. 1988 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Cash Flow Analysis and Back-up. 1989 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Cash Flow Drafts and Prior. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - QMF Disputed Costs. 1990-1991 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - QMF Drawings. 1989-1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -MET Drawings. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - FTL Drawings. 1989-1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - FTL Drawings. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Jaffe Drawings. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - MSI Drawings. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Bash Drawings. 2 folders. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Memos. Folders 1-3. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Memos. Folders 4-7. 1990 (Box 66)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Memos. Folders 8 - 9. 1990 (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Transmittals. 8 Folders. 1989-1990 (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Meeting and Phone Notes. 3 folders. 1989 (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Meeting and Phone Notes. 4, 5, 6 of 6. undated (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Peter Wexler. Notes September and October. 1990 (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - M. Davis. Daily Notes. 1989 (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Punch Lists Annotated by Peter Wexler. undated (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Punch Lists. undated (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Music Stands and Lights Research. undated (Box 67)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Lighting Design as Submitted. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Design as submitted Addendum FTL. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Design as submitted FTL. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Design as submitted FTL fold-up schemes for tension membrane. undated (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Jaffe Sound Bid Package #3. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - FTL Structural Bid Package #1. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Operations Manual MSI. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Operations Manual FTL. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Correspondence Re: Operations. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Site Testing Information. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Possible Staff. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Concert Scheduling. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Scope of Work. Venues. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Fencing. Samples. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Calenders. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Metropolitan Philharmonic. Weekly Production Schedules. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Metropolitan Philharmonic III. Contact Sheet. Background. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Contact Sheets. Current. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Carnegie Hall. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts -Opera Now. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Publicity. Photos. Models. Sketches. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Press and Public Relations. 1988 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Press and Public Relations. Articles and Reviews. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Company Books. 1989 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Credits List Correspondence. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Credits List. Final. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Transmittals. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Concert. 1990 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Transmittals. 1991 (Box 68)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Outgoing Correspondence. 3 folders. 1990 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - QMF Disputed Invoices. undated (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Operations Consultancy Correspondence. 4 folders. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Outgoing Correspondence. 5 folders. 1990-1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Transmittals. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - MPOC Operations MSI Service Call Report. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Operating Consultancy Sound Operator Correspondence. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Sound Operator MTG Motes, Memo. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Sound Operator Candidates Resumes. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Draft Organizational Charts. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Abstracts of Design for Logo. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - QMF Letters - Hinge and Other Problems. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Union Information. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Scheduling. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Contact Sheet. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Schedules. 1990 Season. 1990 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Schedules. Shakedown. Drafts. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Schedules Season. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Draft Daily Running Order. 1991 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Wexler Light Plot and Estimate from AVI. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Channel Groupings. Drafts. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Channel Groupings. Final. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Individual Concert Running Sheet. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Instrument Schedule. Drafts. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Cue Sheets. Drafts. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Cue Sheets. Final. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Proposal and letters not submitted. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Proposal Submitted. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Notes Prior to a Proposal. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Opera. New York Philharmonic. New York Parks Concerts - Incoming Correspondence. 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 11-13)